<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>CodeFly</title><description>A description of CodeFly</description><link>https://CodeFly.nl</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 1 Jul 2020 09:10:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 1 Jul 2020 09:10:03 +0200</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://CodeFly.nl/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://CodeFly.nl/posts/ShopifyARImplementation</guid><title>Implementing Augmented Reality on Your Shopify Store</title><description>Identifying sales objections helps face to face sellers increase their conversion. For online stores, doing the same thing can have even more impact on their sales just due to the potential of scaling these objections can be addressed online.</description><link>https://CodeFly.nl/posts/ShopifyARImplementation</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 08:31:00 +0200</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Implementing Augmented Reality on Your Shopify Store</h1><p>Identifying sales objections helps face to face sellers increase their conversion. For online stores, doing the same thing can have even more impact on their sales just due to the potential of scaling these objections can be addressed online.</p><div>
<br></br>
<img src="https://burst.shopifycdn.com/photos/man-browsing-at-a-guitar-shop.jpg?width=4460&height=4460&exif=1&iptc=1&attachment=man-browsing-at-a-guitar-shop.jpg" width="100%" />
<br></br>
</div><p>A survey showed that 62% of customers prefer to physically interact with an item they consider purchasing and prefer offline stores over ecommerce.</p><p>49% of respondents like physical stores more than online ones because they adore getting things they pay for right away. This shows the biggest sales objection that online shoppers have in comparison to a physical store.<br><br>Augmented Reality solves this sales objection for shoppers on your shopify store by actually allowing them to interact with products.</p><p>3 out of 4 People Aged 16-44 Are Aware of AR and many have used it as forms of entertainment.</p><br></br><iframe width="100%" height="420" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vDNzTasuYEw" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe><h2>How to add AR capabilities to your shopify store?</h2><ol><li><strong>Make sure your theme supports 3D objects.</strong></li></ol><p>Brooklyn, Debut and Narrative themes do which are free.</p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Make sure that your 3D files meet the shopify requirements.</strong></li></ol><ul><li>Recommended size: Less than 6MB<ul><li>Maximum size: 15MB.</li><li>File type: <code>GLB</code></li></ul></li></ul><ol start="3"><li><strong>Upload the 3D file on your product page just like adding an image.</strong></li></ol><p>Just as you add any image to your product page, you can upload these 3D files and your customers can start using them right away.</p><br></br><p>If you do not already have a 3D file, Contact Us and talk to our 3D artists and developers.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://CodeFly.nl/posts/ShopifyMarketingWithTools</guid><title>Market Your Shopify Store by Providing Free Digital Tools</title><description>How adding relevent tools to your onlind store can keep your customers coming back to your store and help your sales.</description><link>https://CodeFly.nl/posts/ShopifyMarketingWithTools</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 08:31:00 +0200</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Market Your Shopify Store by Providing Free Digital Tools</h1><p>Great content can provide your store reputation and leads. As the popularity of content marketing grows, companies compete on the front of content creation. Engaging content that provides value for the audience can do wonder for your Shopify Store.</p><p>But great content by itself is of no value if the attention of your audience is not at your content. Train of Attention, especially online, changes fast.</p><div>
<br>
<img src="https://burst.shopifycdn.com/photos/hands-holding-a-phone.jpg?width=925&exif=1&iptc=1&attachment=hands-holding-a-phone.jpg" width="100%" />
<br></br>
</div><p>Potentially powerful way to get leads and build trust with your audience is to use the ideas of content marketing and applying them to relevant tools that your audience may need on a regular basis.</p><p>This allows your customers to associate your brand with solutions to their problems and can be a major sourse of your inbound marketing.</p><p>Shopify itself uses this way of doing things with good results. They provide <a href="https://www.shopify.com/tools">a full collection of free tools</a> to drive sales of their platform.</p><iframe width="100%" height="420" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NG5XsG5rA2o" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br><p>UberSuggest uses this technique to drive consulting clients. NameCheap uses it to sell domain and hosting by providing free logo maker. This is underused but effective way to do Inbound Marketing.</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>